Salsabil Tarek

Front-End Developer

With 3 years experience in building responsive websites with HTML,CSS,Bootstrap,SASS,JavaScript,JQuery,Pug and frameworks like Angular 8 in agile environment using git as version control, Also have experience in CMS like "Wordpress, Joomla!". I have Knowledge about clean code and care to use it in my Work.

- salsabil.tarek55@gmail.com
- Riyad, Saudi arabia
- in linkedin.com/in/salsabil-tarek-630088a6

- +966 581734214
- salsabil55.github.io/profile/
- github.com/salsabil55

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer DafHolding

10/2019 - Present

Website

• https://www.dafholding.com/

Front-End Developer Pharous

08/2018 - 10/2019

Website

http://pharous.com/

Wordpress Developer

OneHoster

02/2017 - 07/2018

Website

https://onehoster.com/

EDUCATION

Computer Science Faculty of Science

Alexandria , Very Good

SKILLS



PROJECTS

Магі3

https://github.com/salsabil55/Marj3-Scholarships-Opportunity

Belshifa

PharmaCastle

https://demo.pharmacastle.org/

Grow

Odem

• https://github.com/salsabil55/odem

Egyption Medical Syndicate

https://stage.ems-cme.org/

Quiz App

https://www.awesomescreenshot.com/video/3702177

Eldawi sons

http://eldawisons.com/

MSG Egypt

http://www.msgegypt.com/

Tycoon Egypt

http://www.tycoonegy.com/

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Motion Graphic

Animations